[Music]
he
w
[Music]
hello good evening good day everybody
and welcome to this special emergency
live stream which is all about the
recent coup that happened in Bangladesh
the coup that happened yesterday
and in case some of you don't know this
is something I have been speaking about
for quite some time I have actually made
a video I made a video in November last
year almost nine roughly nine months
before before right now in which I laid
out the entire possibility of a US
mediated us-backed uh coup in Bangladesh
which would be actually aimed at India
and I've also been speaking about
Manipur the Manipur issue how it's not a
local Law and Order issue how it's a
bigger geopolitical issue which is
connected to Bangladesh which is
connected to Myanmar I've been speaking
about this for the past year and when
you speak about this you take a risk you
take the risk of looking like an idiot
you take the risk that people are going
to call you a conspiracy theorist but
then this happens and unfortunately I
mean this doesn't give me any pleasure
but I have been Vindicated and what
happened yesterday is exactly as as per
the script that I had put out in
November so yeah that's where we are in
that's what we're going to discuss today
I'm going to take your questions ask me
all your questions ask me the best
questions you can so that we can go
through the entire matter before we do
that let me take a look at who all is
there in the live stream I can see lots
of people as always sarak Singh DD
Tushar kalburgi mahes sha Kel rajat
Duhan Abhishek Sharma pray Paul Daran
Singh toan Chri Vladimir Yanik Captain
Rogers VM ptube Kanan pratique Anila
Anila samit statement jit nikil Nei akat
sankit kunjan trti PA hello Om hello
elohi John V Namaste
akiles Tony hun Sunil prian hello Satish
diasi gorov Singh RMS Martian Sam Satish
hello sushant s PR kande
jasu B edit saket katari C jwal hello NS
TJ Chari who is Afghan married to an
Indian lady congratulations sir good job
indrakanti nobody ABI Ai and and lots of
other people so let's get into the
questions let's get into the questions
uh please please ask me your questions
let me greet some more of you Reinhard
Moses rites DH Arijit NJ Patel Prem
Singh the yogi Narayan PR
pararel great growth of India and
everybody else okay I'm not going to be
able to greet each one of you
individually but thank you so much for
being on this live stream let's take
some
questions
uh okay s of says do you really think
prime minister Narendra Modi will take
some serious steps regarding what's
happening in
Bangladesh excellent question let's
begin here Prime Minister Modi means
India he's the head of the government of
India he's the elected head of state of
the country well who's head of state
technically the president doesn't matter
he's the he's the leader of the country
the elected prime minister so what
options does India have first of all
there's this coup that happened
yesterday in Bangladesh what does it
mean for India is it a good thing for
India is it a bad thing there are
certain Indian YouTubers all right
certain Indian YouTubers who have been
spreading this narrative the past few
weeks and months that f is a
dictator and you will see that some of
these Indian YouTubers they are
officially in connection with the um US
Embassy in India the US diplomatic uh
you know presence in India there's an
official connection there's an official
endorsement there are multiple official
endorsements so the Americans are
playing a similar game in India as well
and some of these YouTubers they had a
very big role to play in influencing the
Indian elections general elections that
happened recently a couple of months ago
in which the JP failed to reach an
absolute majority and if these YouTubers
are promoted by and
and and uh in connection with foreign
countries it means there is foreign
interference in the electoral process of
India which clearly there was so what
does this coup in Bangladesh mean for
India first of all so if you watch the
video that I put out and if you have
been listening to what I've been saying
based on all the evidence that's out
there in the public domain is if you can
connect the dots then here's what the
Bangladesh coup means in India it means
that 1971 is now
finished whatever we achieved in 1971
will be undone you see 1971 was a
gigantic slap in the face for the United
States of
America for the for for well in the in
the 20th century they failed a few times
like Vietnam Etc and 71 was a gigantic
failure for the US they had staked a lot
in this they were supporting the
genocide of Hindus by Pakistan in East
Pakistan
Bangladesh read the book The Blood
telegram okay in which their own
Ambassador reports about what's
happening in bangl in East Pakistan and
it's blindingly obvious glaringly
obvious that the Americans were
supporting and aiding and abetting the
genocide of
innocent millions in East Pakistan at
the hands of the Pakistani government
the Americans have a a track record of
being on the on the wrong side of
History so they were doing this and
India had to intervene because the
Pakistan is started attacking India from
East Pakistan so long story short India
had to intervene and when the war
started the 71 War started the Americans
sent an aircraft carrier strike group in
the sea of in the in the Bay of
Bengal to bully India to arm twist India
and not just that the British also sent
an aircraft carrier strike group so
there were two aircraft carrier strike
groups in the Bay of Bengal aimed at
India and the objective was to stop
India from from continuing its military
operation so that the pakistanis could
peacefully conduct the genocide that's
what the Americans and the British
wanted but the
USSR was involved also and they
had they had sent a nuclear submarine
group in the Bay of Bengal so when the
Americans in the British reach there
they find Soviet nuclear submarines
waiting for them and that's why they
were not able to arm twist India
otherwise the 71 War would have been a
disaster for India so India is able to
liberate Bangladesh it has nothing to do
with the MTI bahini which was a rag tag
Guerilla outfit supported by India it
was the Indian army that liberated
Bangladesh and we should actually in my
opinion
have
reabsorbed Bangladesh with back into
India it was outside of India just for
20 odd years and it was Indian Territory
for thousands of years so we failed to
do that we failed to reintegrate
Bangladesh into India after liberating
it after conquering it we had the right
of
Conquest that's a conqueror's right to
to take the territory but it's our
people
now they're no longer our people most of
them so that's what happens and that is
a disaster for the us we win the war we
we VI vict Pakistan we break Pakistan
into two a new nation is created and it
was a disaster it was a humiliation for
the US that's 71 in 1973 let's go to the
map where's the map because I have to
explain with the map so in response to
this humiliation the Americans don't
just sit down and take it lying down
they go to the map and I'm going to go
to the map and I'm going to show you
what they
did okay so where's the map let's put
that on the screen so in 1971 after this
thing happens the Americans go to the
map and they acquire the territory of
Theo garciaa the British Indian
Territory in the in the Indian Ocean
region and they convert that into it it
it is illegally taken from Maus it is
part of macius but the British have
given it to the Americans the Americans
have established a military base here a
big
Naval base and Air Force Base the Air
Force Base can can accommodate the
largest aircraft in the world military
aircraft in the world and the Naval Base
can accommodate aircraft carriers that's
how big and powerful this base is and
they use this to project power in the
region so that was a a reaction to the
1971 humiliation that the Americans
faced now what the Americans have done
yesterday by ejecting shik Hina from
from Bangladesh and and by creating this
visuals of the of the destruction of the
statues of shik mujur rman just like
what happened in Iraq after Saddam
Hussein's defeat they are portraying
this lady and her father as dictators
and they are undoing everything that was
done in and after
1971 so what we are seeing now my
friends is the reestablishment of East
Pakistan at the behest of the US this is
a US operation the Americans are behind
this let's be very clear about that I
will not mince words I'm saying this
openly the Americans are behind this now
what's going to happen the Americans
will sooner or later acquire this island
over here for some reason it's called
what some some Christian name St
Martin's Island this is the Bangladeshi
Island and they will create a new Diego
Garcia here a Naval Base Air Force Base
and and terrorist training base or
Freedom Fighter training base over here
they will train various guerillas and
insurgents who will fight against Burma
and India
and from here they will station fighter
planes and and longdistance strategic
bombers and whatnot and they'll be able
to project power not just over India but
also over
China okay that's what it gives them and
soon you will see the The Carving out of
a Christian Nation out of parts of
Bangladesh and parts of Burma and
eventually the Americans want parts of
Manipur and mizoram also to be part of
it then that nation is part of project k
which is Project cookie land a nation a
cookie land for Christ so that is what
we are seeing so now the question is
will prime minister Narendra Modi take
some serious steps regarding what's
happening in Bangladesh so we we have to
understand here that we we cannot be
emotional in this matter do not be
emotional be
realistic where does India stand when it
comes to
power how powerful is
India compared to the US compared to
China compared to whoever else so let me
put something else on the screen I I was
supposed to unve this I'll do it
soon this is my Global Power Rankings
which I was which I will soon release to
the
public and this is the top 20 Nations a
list of the top 20 Nations okay and each
nation has a hard power score that I
have calculated based on open source
data and my own calculations my own
let's say formula
formulas so the US there's a hard power
score of 93 it is the only
superpower it's it's one of the four
genuinely Sovereign Nations Russia comes
second with a hard power score of 54 it
is a near
superpower it is about half as powerful
as the us but very very powerful China
comes third at 15 it is less than
onethird of that of Russia the hard
power score that's how weak China is
compared to Russia and the US and India
is less than five okay it is India is
about onethird of the hard power score
of China less than one third so if you
compare India with the US the US is
about 20 20 plus times more powerful
than India do you think a nation that is
that that is 20 times less powerful than
the US do you think it can stand up to
the US
it's not possible the brutal reality of
the world is India is not powerful
enough right now to to prevent the US
from doing what it wants forget about
India the Tha the Chinese whether you
whether you accept it or not whether you
like it or not they claim that Taiwan is
their territory and Taiwan is in China's
backyard China is right next door to CH
Taiwan is right next door to China are
the Chinese able to take it back
China is way more powerful than India
right more than three times more
powerful China is not able to take back
Taiwan which is in right in its own
backyard that's how powerful the
Americans are that's how much power
projection the American capabilities the
Americans have so far away from American
Shores and the same thing in India in
the Indian Ocean region in the Indian
subcontinent so right now I think India
will be lucky if we don't lose Manipur
and
mam okay the Americans are fully
capable of doing what they want they are
fully capable of reducing India to the
level of Cuba through through economic
sanctions so right now there is not much
India can do what we can do is we can
Safeguard the territorial integrity and
sovereignty of India of the Far East of
India which is Manipur mizoram Etc that
the Americans are trying to influence
the Mayhem that's been happening in
since May last year the cookie
terrorists terrorizing the native people
of Manipur that is all engineered by the
west where are these cookie terrorist
getting their unlimited supplies of arms
and ammunition from it's coming in from
Burma so are the Chinese providing it or
or is somebody else providing it that's
the only
question and I assure you this Mayhem
that's happening in in Myanmar in
Burma it also affects China negatively
they will also definitely try to take
advantage of it in the past the Chinese
have very much been in support of
various separatist groups in all across
India's Far East all across from mizoram
to Manipur nagaland to Assam to wherever
the Chinese have supported that in the
20th century but right now this
operation project K is an American
operation okay and they very much have
the upper hand and they have succeeded
in evicting in ejecting fhina and you
must have heard that they the UK has
recently I mean just a couple of hours
ago they announced that they have denied
Asylum to shik Hina and the Americans
have canceled shik hass's Visa which
means that she cannot travel to the West
which means that she will have to stay
in India so now they will be able to
portray India as a nation that supports
dictators and they will be able to
successfully portray shik kazina as a
Indian stouge so that will inflame
sentiments further in Bangladesh and
various Indian YouTubers and
intellectuals will will
support this narrative that is what
we're going to
see and if India takes any serious steps
okay what can India do right now India
can seal off the border between India
various Indian States and Bangladesh we
can impose nighttime curfew or whatever
we can make sure that nobody crosses
over which means the poor Hindus of
Bangladesh will be left to to their
Fates okay beyond that India can't do
anything beyond that what can India do
uh
if India tries to interfere in any way
in Bangladesh the Americans will accuse
of accuse us of being an imperialistic
hegemonic nation and they will impose
milit economic sanction on India if
India does anything about the lacks of
cookie terrorists who have crossed over
into Manipur in the past few years
foreign illegal infiltrators if India
does anything about that the Americans
will say that India is uh you know
carrying out an anti-christian program
in the Far East of India and they will
impose economic sanctions which will
destroy the Indian
economy so right now there is nothing
much India can do this is just a simple
fact it's a simple fact of
life that's where we are so the best we
can hope for in in the coming weeks
months and coming few years is that
India doesn't lose any territory to the
Americans or their proxies their proxies
like the cookies and the new Pakistan
East Pakistan and Bangladesh so right
now there is not much that India can do
and that is just a realistic observation
people can you know make all kinds of
emotional
statement see I see all kinds of
so-called intellectuals and analysts
making very strong statements words
versus actions please understand we are
not in a position to do much about this
the truth is that the Americans are way
more powerful than us even in our own
neighborhood okay we still aren't able
to access Central Asia or Eurasia
because of their proxies in Pakistan and
much more so essentially India now the
situation is that India is essentially
encircled now to our West we have
Pakistan which is a US proxy a very
hostile
Nation it cuts off our access to Europe
and to Central Asia we can't even reach
Afghanistan by road to our North we have
Chinese occupied Tibet another hostile
Nation so we can't reach Eurasia through
that uh we have the sea route obviously
which is open in the East you have a new
hostile Nation
Bangladesh it's being it's been taken
over by anti-india forces and sooner or
later it looks like there will be a new
cookie land which will be carved out of
Burma which will cut off India's access
to Southeast
Asia now if India takes any military
action India will be devastated by
economic sanctions so right now there is
nothing India can do there is no
short-term solution to this problem
the long-term solution will take at
least 20 years and that is nothing but
the same solution as the solution to the
Manipur problem we have to become much
more economically and Military powerful
militarily powerful we have to rise to
such an extent that nobody can impose
economic sanctions upon us because it
will be harmful to them as well and then
we can take care of our neighborhood
slowly in whatever way we see we deem is
best so there is no short-term solution
to this problem prime minister Narendra
Modi is going to have to
there there's nothing no no no drastic
steps he can
take prati V says who could be behind
the coup is it the us or China or some
other power you know there are certain
analysts I see on Twitter Etc who are
saying it could be
China I I would urge you to watch the
video that I put out on the 4th of
November 2023 in which I have given you
a list a series of of uh you know
evidence a bunch of evidence
chronological
evidence it shows a clear pattern that
points to the US okay now they and I'll
show I'll tell you what the students the
so-called students who think that they
are behind this entire Uprising uh their
leadership whatever it is has now
proposed that this guy called Muhammad
yunus should be the interim caretaker of
whatever prime minister of Bangladesh
now Muhammad Inus is very very deeply
involved with the US he obviously is
beholden to the US and to the West they
gave him a Nobel Prize he was the the
guy behind graming Bank he's a very
well-known Western
stouge um the opposition parties in
Bangladesh are all known to be W you
know allied with the West the the
American you know Embassy and Consul at
Bangladesh had been meeting with these
political parties for months before last
before this the general election in
Bangladesh this year there's a clear
pattern they the Americans announced
they would impose sanctions on any
individual who would be anti-democratic
or whatever in Bangladesh it is clear
and and shik Hina herself said multiple
times that the Americans are trying to
carve out a Christian Nation out of
Bangladesh and Burma and India and she
said that they had told her that if she
allows them to do this then they will
allow her to to win the election
unopposed without any problems and they
have also demanded that St Martin's
Island it is a it is very clear that the
US is behind this
okay it's absolutely clear and this is
something that's going to affect China
also so right now if you look at the
subcontinent we are kind of encircled
and on two sides you have pakistans East
Pakistan West Pakistan we should start
calling Bangladesh East Pakistan again
in my opinion and you will soon have
kiland which will be another us proxy
Nepal is a Chinese proxy uh maldiv is a
Chinese proxy Sri Lanka was a failed
Chinese proxy right now it's nowhere and
so on so we are surrounded by other
nations proxies which is what happens
when you are not strong
enough okay so India is right now not
strong enough India is at best a
regional power a regional power at best
it is the most powerful nation in the
subcontinent but right now it looks
helpless because more powerful more
powerful nations are involved in the
subcontinent with the objective of
completely encircling India and that's
where we find ourselves right
now Krishna says is it a failure from
bat intelligence services and government
in ating or containing the current
situation in Bangladesh bhat was sucing
successful in averting regime change
plan during Bangla elections see in the
case of Bangladesh it has been very
clear that the Americans are trying to
get rid of shik Hina and to bring back
the anti-india forces in power in
Bangladesh so the Indian intelligence
and the Indian government Etc diplomatic
core everybody knew about this so there
is no failure when it comes to the to
the Bangladesh issue the coup that
happened yesterday no matter what India
did it was going to happen I'll tell you
where we have succeeded F Kina has come
out of this alive otherwise she would
have been treated the same way Saddam
Hussein or or mamar Gaddafi that that's
what could have happened it is because
of Indian because of the Indian
involvement that she was able to be
extracted out of Bangladesh safe and
sound so uh when you are faced with a
with a power that is with a nation that
is like 20 25 times more powerful than
you then no matter how much intelligence
you have there's nothing you can do
about them about things so that is where
we are it's not a failure of the Indian
intelligence agencies it is simply that
India isn't strong enough India isn't
powerful enough and that's something we
could have done something about I mean
we could have reabsorbed Bangladesh in
1971 now that's not Mr modi's fault that
we did not reabsorb Bangladesh in 1971
and let's say we did not reabsorb
Bangladesh in 71 then when there was a
coup in Bangladesh and shik mujibur rman
was killed and his entire family was
wiped out apart from his daughter shik
Hina and her family then why didn't
India interfere immediately that was the
US and the West re retaking some kind of
control in Bangladesh so India dropped
the ball multiple times when it comes to
Bangladesh if you look at the the
majority of the Bangladeshi population
today they are pro Pakistan and anti-
India how did we allow this to happen to
a nation that we essentially helped
create so that is a continuous series of
failures over the past 50 years from the
part of the various Indian governments
so I would not say that the current
Indian intelligence services are are
responsible for what's happened there's
nothing they could have done we have
we've just gone too far failure after
failure after failure that's why this
has happened we simply did not have any
interest in projecting power even within
our own
neighborhood and now we are doing it but
it's kind of quite late isn't it so yeah
I I I don't blame the Indian
intelligence agencies for this
particular matter or the government of
India not this particular
matter now Raj Chopra asks a very good
question if something like yesterday
what happened in Bangladesh happens in
Barat what could what will or should be
the action plan of the common common man
and the government also touch upon how
illegal immigrant situation should could
go in Barat
now so look how did the coup happen in
Bangladesh the coup happened not because
of the
students okay understand this there were
student protest blah blah blah students
running Riot on the streets blah blah
blah all that stuff is that why shikina
left is that why she had to flee the
country absolutely not understand what
power
is she had to flee because the Army gave
her 45
minutes who holds the real power what is
power at the end of the day like Maat
said political power flows out of the
barrel of a
gun power is the threat of violence
power is the capacity to unleash
violence on demand various kinds and
various forms of violence various levels
of violence that is what power is power
is on the
streets power is
military so the students look as long as
the police obeyed shikh as long as the
Army was in line with shika there's
nothing those students could have done
it's because the Army took the side of
the students supposedly the students
that she had to
leave understand that so the Army
betrayed the nation the Army sold out
the nation to the Americans that's what
happened that that that guy who gave a
press conference uh Waker something or
the whatever his name is I can't
pronounce those names so that's what
happened now so the way to sell this
coup to the world is by creating this
Narrative of student protests that these
young innocent idealistic students are
fed up with the dictatorial regime of
Sheik Hina and they have gone out on the
streets and they' have been facing the
brunt of the security forces and
eventually the military had a change of
heart and then they supported the
students so the military are the good
guys the students are the good guys and
shika is the bad guy that is how the
narrative is spun but what did the coup
is the Army taking the side of the US
that is what sealed the coup that is the
coup itself the Army switching
Allegiance from their country to the US
that's the coup now can something like
that happen in
Bat well in bhat that can't happen if
you see I not go into the into the uh
theory of what's behind a coup uh if you
look at my channel a couple of years
back there's a podcast with a gentleman
called Dr Edward
lutwak he's one of the foremost geost
strategists in the world he has advised
governments and prime ministers and
presidents okay and he is the author of
a book called Keta a practical
handbook and it is said that in in a CO
in a failed C somewhere in Africa the
general who was trying to carry out the
coup he was shot and then when they
found his body inside his court there
was this book so that's actually kind of
a manual of how to carry out a coup and
if you study that book it will become
clear why a c daa cannot happen in India
a military coup can't happen in India
there are a set of conditions that have
to be satisfied for a nation to be open
to such kind of such coups China a coup
can happen in China the US a CP can
happen in India in the US but in India
coup can't happen for a variety of
reasons read the book if you're
interested so a military coup can't
happen in India okay but what can happen
in India is that the Americans can
unleash student protest farma protest
various kind of protests they have are
already indulging in what they call
subnational diplomacy in India allegedly
which means that they're allegedly uh
reaching out through their diplomats and
proxies to various state governments in
India allegedly
allegedly state governments that
allegedly don't have allegedly good
relations with the center okay that's
what I what that's what people are
alleging so the Americans are trying to
create further divisions you know the
the United States is an Empire it is a
continuation of the British Empire and
they have the same tried and tested
policy of divide and Rule divide and
conquer so create divisions within a
nation make the people fight each other
and
then make hay so that's what the America
already already doing the entire Indian
academ academic system is corrupt rotten
to the core and the Modi government has
done nothing to change that in the past
10 years yeah very disappointingly so
the the the the left the
leftists who are anti-indian have a
strangle hold on the academic system all
the most of the academic staff
professors lecturers readers Etc
especially in human ities
departments uh they are strongly
leftist and they are you will find if
you go deep inside that all the
literature they produce is anti-india
anti-hindu Hindu phobic all that and
that is very much in line with the
agenda of various Western Powers so
these professors who write anti-india
stuff and produce anti-india research in
in in large quantities they are given
all kinds of uh you know Wonderful
goodies from the West by the West they
are invited to give lectures they are
treated like like
VIPs and they given all kinds of
honors and when you are treated so well
why would you not want that to continue
so the entire academic system especially
in the humanities is more or less not
entire but most of it is anti-india and
you could say the West controls
it so if you want to create chaos in
India all you have to do is activate
your agents your asset in various
academic you know University College
departments there's a whole network and
just unleash student protest students
are idealistic students are clueless I
when I was 20 I was clueless about the
world I had read a lot but I had no idea
how the world really works I was
absolutely clueless okay I've been there
so I'm not saying the students who go
out and protest are bad people no they
are good kids they are idealistic they
genuinely believe they're doing
something good for them nation and that
idealism and that naivity is prayed upon
by their their their teachers the
professors they are the
ones who need to be looked at so then
it's so it's extremely easy to unleash
hordes of students on the streets and
they are filled with this righteous
anger the students and in India in the
Indian academic system you essentially
worship people in Authority people in
positions of power and authority right
whatever they say you believe it
wholeheartedly you never question them
that's what you brainwashed into being
like so your programming kicks in
whatever they say you go and do it and
that's how you can unleash student
protests all across India that is going
to
happen I'm going out on limb today right
now I'm going to I'm saying this it's
going to happen the next two three years
student protests in various parts of
India we will also have the farmer
protests reactive ated and various other
kinds of protests so it will not be a
kud but it's going to be the Americans
will try and destabilize the nation step
by step by step by activating various
assets and networks of facets that they
have see what are the Americans
concerned about when it comes to India
India is projected to be the next big
thing
economically okay uh if you look at a
the economic projections for India uh on
a 2035 2040 Horizon India will be a very
powerful very large economy okay India
by 2050 could very much
uh could very much surpass
China and that is something that the
Americans are very concerned about
because uh okay someone saying there is
lag is there lag in the
video is there a
lag I'm seeing comments that says that
there is a lag in the video or
audio okay it's better now it's better
now okay so the point is the Americans
are concerned that India see the the
Americans have already made a huge
mistake when it comes to China they
aided and abetted and midwifed the rise
of China and they want to make sure they
don't let this happen again when it
comes to India so India they see India
as a long-term
adversary especially a nation that
refuses to be a western sto a nation
that has an independent foreign policy a
nation that still has an ancient
polytheistic culture how dare we have
that so they will do their best to
destroy
India right now they're containing India
they're encircling India eventually they
want to destroy India balkanize India
they want to baniz India so you can
expect various kinds of destabilization
activities to happen in India over the
next two three four five years okay and
the illegal immigrants will be very much
part of it because these illegal
immigrants when we talk about illegal
immigrants who are we talking about
we're talking about Bangladesh's between
50 to 100 million we're talking about
ringas who have been coming in since the
2010s and we're talking about maybe a
million cookies who have come in in the
past
whatever period of time so these people
have no allegiance to India they have no
affiliation or or uh anything to do with
Indian culture and they can be
activated so when we want to destabilize
a nation and you have 100 million
foreign infiltrators in the nation
illegals and yeah you can activate those
assets to destabilize the
nation so what should be the action plan
of the
government what should be the action
plan
of the go once again there's a
lag that's interesting we don't have
lags otherwise don't do
we okay I hear there's a lag come on
internet
connection so
look okay I think the lag is gone now so
the point
is the point is these illegals can be de
activated and used to destabilize the
nation various assets can be used so
what can the government do the
government will have to crack down on
illegal infiltration I think the
government of India should now
repatriate or or take steps to
repatriate Bangladesh out of India which
could cause possibly a lot of chaos so
you either allow the bangladeshis to
stay in India and become part of the
population and become a long-term
demographic threat or you bite the
bullet and do what is unpleasant
identify them round them up and throw
them out of India maybe we should send
them to the US border H maybe we should
arrange for the bangladeshis illegal
bangladeshis in India to be sent to the
US the US can absorb them 100 million
bangladeshis but they won't do that so
we should repatriate them to
Bangladesh that's what I would say and
somebody's talking about the chicken
neck yeah we have to be very careful
about the chicken neck the Siliguri
Corridor which is well Bangladesh is
very much present there uh so the
government of India is going to have its
hands full there's going to
be
more
attempts ongoing attempts over the next
few years to destabilize India to make
India look weak to to hamper the Indian
economic growth to hamper the prospect
of foreign investment in
India to worsen India's internal
security situation and much more
so the government of India the
intelligence agencies need to be need to
be on top of
this and they need to find ways to
prevent this from happening or if it is
happening then they need to be able to
clamp down on that very fast the common
man what can the common man do
nothing
nothing geopolitical dub says how does
Russia see it can you explain the
situation from Russia's perspective okay
so Russia's perspec perspective look I'm
not sure if the Russians have said
anything about this thus far if they
have I I've not been aware of it but
let's look at Russia's interest okay
strategic interest in the subcontinental
region Russia is this B big giant
country which is
essentially immune to Western sanctions
American
sanctions uh it is closely aligned with
China because China is a gigantic
economy the world's second largest
economy and the Russians depend on that
they are also aligned
well Loosely aligned so to say with
India there is a tremendous amount of
trust and comfort when it comes to India
not with China China is an adversary
actually and the Russians are aligned
with Iran and Syria and so on
now so from the Russian perspective if
India is in full control of the
subcontinent and in and India is a
strong Rising power it is good for them
it is good for Russia and if the
Americans are able to make inroads in
the subcontinent and and destabilize the
subcontinent and put India on the back
foot and essentially encircle India and
remove a pro pro-india government from
Bangladesh then it it weakens India and
it is overall bad for Russia so from a
big picture perspective from a 30,000 ft
perspective Russia sees this as a very
bad development and they would not be
impressed at uh what India is doing
right now they would say India India
should have should be doing better India
should not be allowing this to happen
but they will also understand that there
is nothing much India can do right now
because the Americans are so powerful so
this is part of the push and pull of
geopolitics geopolitics is the
geopolitical situation in the world is
evolving very rapidly right now the
world threatens to become a multi-polar
world the Americans want to ensure it
never becomes multi-polar they want a
bipolar World us China and keep Russia
out but the real Nation they worry about
the fear is Russia and they see India as
the only long-term big adversarial uh Na
that could become an adversary and they
want to ensure it never happens they
will prevent it from happening uh so
from the Russian perspective this is not
a good development they would not be
happy with what's happened in
Bangladesh T Chandra says do you think
the Indian government has been taken off
guard given we have NSA Ajit D Dr J
Shankar and other clever people in power
you may have the cleverest people in
power but if you are not powerful enough
there's nothing you can
do all right if if Henry Kissinger had
been the foreign minister of the
Maldives he was super clever clever
wasn't he Henry
kinger but had he been the the foreign
minister of the Maldives do you think he
would have been able to do anything if
somebody tried to invade the Maldives no
so it doesn't matter how clever your
people are if your nation is not
powerful then all the cleverness is
wasted all right okay here we have a lag
again
here we have a
lag
apparent lagging and restoring lagging
and
restoring I don't get it why is it like
that is it still lagging gentlemen and
ladies
people are saying it's fine
now
um the video is lagging but the audio is
fine the Deep state is involved in the
lag CIA is taking
control the Matrix doesn't want me to
speak who knows who
knows uh okay not a major lag
still
lagging CIA
lag
okay
uh next question should India try to
develop good relations with Bangladesh
like it's doing with the Maldives
despite their anti-india stance or
should India cut off all thighs and seal
the
Border uh is it still lagging
okay let me just uh one second okay I'm
going to
okay I hope that may have hopefully
solved the
problem anyway I'm going to speak about
this so what should India do about this
should India close the border and cut
off all ties no that doesn't make any
sense it doesn't make sense for uh India
to cut off relations with
Bangladesh and just seal the Border we
can certainly seal the Border but
there's no point shutting down relations
with Bangladesh we have to you know
continue some kind of relationship we
have to try and make it as to work as
best as possible the way we are dealing
with the
Maldives and yeah that's what I would
say the video is still lagging good
God okay that's
interesting okay give me a second I'll
try and change some settings if I
can I mean you can hear the voice but
there should be
also the image should also be there just
give me a second
please
e
e e
hello I am sorry about that hopefully
things are better now are
they I have changed my connection it's
the show has not ended I'm
back uh okay I hope it works fine
now I'm not visible am I visible hello
can you see me can you hear
me can you hear me am I visible Anisha
says it's
better yes most likely CIA did
that it starts lagging when you name the
soul superpower anyhow I think uh we are
back on track now uh so my okay coming
back to the last question India should
not cut off ties with
Bangladesh we still have some kind of
ties with Pakistan we still have some
ties with Maldives with the Maldives we
have ties with turkey
Etc so and we also have a relationship
with China despite it being an adversary
relationship relationship so the point
is we should not cut off our
relationship with Bangladesh We should
strive to make it work in some way a CP
on AC Channel looks like somebody tried
to do a here but yes it did not
succeed okay Ana says can Donald Trump
coming to power help India no Donald
Trump coming to power will make no
difference because the by now I think it
should be I hope I think it should be
obvious to everybody that the president
of the United States is not the real
person who is in power okay there is an
unelected Hado we bunch of people who
actually run the United States who are
really in power in the
US you can call it whatever you want you
can call it the swamp you can like the
Donald Trump like Donald Trump says you
can call it the Deep state it is those
people who run the US and am I am I
pulling these opinions out of a hat no
you have a president and a vice
president who are essentially
nonfunctional right now in the US Joe
Biden is we don't even know if he's dead
or alive it looks like they have body
doubles of him and even those body
doubles are like all shaken and all
right they're not fully here he clearly
if it's still Joe byen he clearly has
dementia he is no longer capable of
running a country and Kamala Harris I
mean do you think she's capable of
running a country clearly she's not but
the country is running itself somebody
is running the
country and we do know that when Trump
was in power the last time from 2016 to
2020 he was thwarted at every step the
establishment
conspired and came together to thwart
him at every step they did not allow him
to to achieve any of the things he
wanted to achieve I was really surprised
that he was not taken out while he was
President 1963 style so if he comes back
to Power I don't think it can help India
Bangladesh is now a new Pakistan it's
now East Pakistan and Trump coming back
to Power will change nothing the US
foreign policy will not change
the US hostility towards India will not
change nothing will change so Trump
coming back to Power will make no
difference John the wise says should
India give Asylum to the Bangladeshi PM
shik Hina and and take a stand against
fundamentalists we will have to give
Asylum to her most likely uh the West
has closed their doors to her I think
she would have preferred to go to the
west to the UK or to the US or somewhere
else perhaps looks like it won't be
happening uh after her family was
massacred by the generals in the 1970s
she spent a few years in New Delhi as as
a young lady so I think she's going to
have to spend a few more years in New
Delhi it looks like or somewhere in
India U so in case she doesn't get
Asylum elsewhere we certainly
should give Asylum to her in that case
the Americans will succeed in painting
shikina as an Indian stoe and they will
also succeed in painting India as a
nation that
Harbors dictators but that's just what
it is uh when it comes to these
fundamentalists they obviously are our
enemies so we should take a stand
against them for sure no
doubt okay this is not a Bangladesh
question what's my skin CLE skin care is
glowing I I just wash my face with soap
that's it I'm a guy no skin
care U
okay aninda bachari says implications of
the Bangladesh situation in tripura so
once again let's go to the map there is
tripura in case our some of our Indian
viewers Etc don't know about it tripura
is this state in India's Far East the
capital is agartala which is right on
the border between India and and East
Pakistan and yeah it's a state tripura
is a state with a sign significantly
long border with Bangladesh it's ENT
essentially surrounded on three sides by
Bangladesh so India will have to be
extra vigilant in the state of
tripura
uh and we will have to probably
reinforce the presence of the border
security force and whoever else is
involved in the Border
regions and yeah there could be problems
in this in this region
uh maybe there could be more attempts to
infiltrate uh terrorists or whatever
into
India now that there is an East Pakistan
like situation in India various
Insurgent groups and separatist groups
from India's Far East uh they whoever
whichever of those proxies still exist
in Bangladesh they still exist they'll
be
reactivated and they will try to forment
trouble in India's Far East so that will
happen in tripura AUST is one of these
states which is a border state with
Bangladesh so we will have to be extra
careful in tripura and other states in
this region so yes it has uh it
definitely has implications for the
security situation in tripura obviously
the Bangladeshi Armed Forces aren't
capable of invading tripura or any such
thing but they could certainly
infiltrate terrorists in various uh uh
agents of various kinds into rura which
would be bad for us so we we will have
to be extra V
Vigilant
um shashwat says why does shikida want
to go to the US when they were behind
dethroning her I think she was she
wanted to go some go to some country in
the west maybe the UK so generally what
you find is that when there is a coup in
some Nation let's say Pakistan then
typically uh the the president prime
minister whoever it is who has deposed
they typically go and settle down in the
UK the UK is is the safe haven for all
these people uh and it generally has an
open door policy as long as you come
with lots of money they will ask no
questions okay it's the money laundering
capital of the world I'm talking about
London essentially and the UK is a poor
Nation that's attached to London so shik
H most likely wanted to go to the UK and
if in case you're not aware uh some of
the people who were involved in the
assassination of shik H's father Sheik
bujur Rahman and his extend in his
family some of those people some of
those Killers who are convicted killers
they are living free in London or
somewhere in the UK some are also living
in the US and Canada allegedly
allegedly uh so I guess some of what
that's the reason why she wanted to go
and stay in the UK good living standards
she probably has good amount of money uh
and uh yeah probably that's what she was
intending but the UK obviously is as we
know to not put it very delicately the
UK is a lap dog of the US it's a wasal
state of the US and they will do what
the American their American Masters tell
them so they have denied entry to her
and well now she probably is stuck in
India
okay Clash of Clans says why are you
saying that Bangladesh is now the new
Pakistan what do you mean by that please
explain
it's we should start calling Bangladesh
East Pakistan again why do I say that
it's because the
see the
coup I'm not going to re reate
everything I have stated in the past
hour but let me just give you the brief
uh a brief breakdown the US is behind
the coup by conducting this coup the
Americans have undone the events of
1971 they have brought back a pro us
anti- anti- India government in pakist
in in in Bangladesh the the the
political parties that are now going to
be in power in Bangladesh are very
strongly Pro Pakistan Pro us and
anti-india which was a situation before
1971 and they are visibly they're making
a point to make a big show of destroying
statues of shikh mujibur Rahman who was
the architect of the 19 who is
essentially considered to be the father
of the nation of Bangladesh so you
destroy the statues of the father of the
nation of Bangladesh you are destroying
the ethos and the idea of Bangladesh
you're going back to the days of East
Pakistan so that's what I mean by that
in very
brief CV says we should take military
action after a few years in undo mistake
of
1971 uh sir you should pay attention
when I speak we aren't powerful
enough we aren't powerful enough to
stand up to the
US Bangladesh is now a US proxy
we send one soldier across the border
the Americans will impose economic
sanctions on
India okay and their economic sanctions
can devastate Nations you know people
say that Venezuela is a failed nation a
failed economy because of socialism
that's not true what destroyed Venezuela
is not socialism it's American
sanctions what destroyed Cuba is not
socialism it's American
sanctions what destroyed Iran is not
whatever is in place is there it's
American
sanctions the Americans can destroy a
nation with
sanctions okay so we we we need to be
careful you think of taking military
action you send you send one soldier
across the border into the territory of
an American proxy it's going to be hell
for you and they're waiting for you to
make a mistake doesn't work like that
this is not child's play here this is
the real world the real world is very
complicated and I understand that you
won't get it because there are so many
things that layers of layers of things
that are hidden from view takes a lot of
time to uncover all
that
um is correct Rin
sabun okay mlin says why does the US
want the St Martin's Island they already
have military bases in Diego Garcia and
Pakistan why go through so much trouble
for a
third okay so where is Theo
garciaa it's right over here it's the
southernmost part of the uh of the
uh Andaman chos uh archipelago so the
distance between dieo garciaa roughly
and India southernmost tip of India is
about 2,000 kilometers okay and if you
want to calculate the distance between
Diego
Garcia and let's say Lassa okay China is
occupied
Tibet it is about roughly 4 and a half
th000
kilm now let's say they acquire St
Martin's Island this one here now let's
calculate the distance from here to
Lassa it's about 1,000 kilometers 1/4th
almost 1/ fifth of the distance from
dieo Garcia to Lassa and dieo Garcia to
let's say dieo Garcia to
Delhi okay roughly from there to Delhi
how much is it New
Delhi uh here so dieo to Delhi is 4,000
kilm and St Martin's Island to Delhi is
how
much how much how much how
much it's way lesser than that so you
can see that by acquiring a military
base in this island they they get much
closer to China they get much closer to
India they much get much closer to Delhi
they can genuinely project power in this
region they can project power I mean if
if St Martin is the is the center of a
circle and you create a circle with a
1,000 km 2,000 km radius can you see how
much coverage the get of power
projection they can project power deep
into India and into China why not get
that and what's the trouble what trouble
does it what is the trouble for them in
in making a new military base they have
hundreds of military bases all across
the world what is one more for them they
have the money they have the means it's
no big deal for them it'll be up and
running running in in in less than a
year or two there's no trouble there so
that's why they want St Martin's Island
to first of all put this umbrella of
protection on their proxy which is
Bangladesh put their umbrella of
protection and air strikes and all that
over all of Burma Myanmar and project
power over India as well as China at the
same time and also Thailand and all the
other nations Indonesia Etc the more the
merrier military bases so it makes a
tremendous mendous amount of sense from
the American perspective to acquire that
Island it's a it's a great thing for
them if they can acquire it they'll get
it now they will certainly get it
now okay now let's take some questions
that I haven't hopefully answered I'm
getting similar questions see once again
the same
question
um Immortal says will Russia help India
if Pakistan Bangladesh and the West
attack India today do you think India
Will Survive or our suffering
civilization will end
look if Pakistan and Bangladesh attack
India okay first of all let's talk about
Pakistan if Pakistan attacks India we
can end Pakistan in 15 minutes without
having to go nuclear we can do
that so Pakistan is no big deal
Bangladesh is not even a match for India
okay Bangladesh is its military strength
is essentially negligible compared to
that of India if India and Bangladesh go
to war which I never want to see happen
it's our I mean it's our territory it's
our people essentially at the end of the
day even though they are no longer our
people but if such a war happens India
versus Bangladesh it's going to be a
one-sided War the it's like in in a
football match you have a 30 score line
that sort of thing so if bang Pakistan
and Bangladesh get together to to attack
India once again it's going to be a
clear victory for India if the West gets
involved well look the West doesn't want
to go to war with India the West which
means the US doesn't want to go to war
with India they want to hamper India's
economic R so if India is projected to
keep growing at let's say 8% for the
next 20 years they want India to grow at
4 and a half% for the next 20 years that
sort of economic decline they want to
see that India should not reach its
potential India should not become a
major economy by 2035 by 2040 India
should not reach the $15 trillion Mark
by 35 India should be at 8 trillion by
2035 that's what they want stagnation so
the entire moral of the nation
crumbles the Vitality of the nation goes
away people become pessimistic people
invest more in English language
education and go to the West whoever can
and within India there is infighting and
problems and riots and whatnot
separatism that's what they want they
don't want to go to war with India do
you understand
that so so Russia doesn't have to get
involved in this matter because there's
no
war but yeah India will have to play its
cards right because that is what the
West wants they want to ensure India
doesn't grow that India fragments
crumbles India gets balkanized even if
India doesn't get balkanized there are
tremendous amounts of problems within
India internal problems disunity
infighting slow growth the nean rate of
growth that sort of stuff and that's
what they're trying to
engineer okay
okay I've answered the Chinese question
lots of times so I'll not go there the
Chinese are most likely not involved in
this Bangladesh
matter utar sodia says this is a never
ending game isn't it well geopolitics is
a never ending game there always a push
and pull push and pull it's a never
ending game you you never there's no
final Victory
ever okay so for example when kanishka
the Great conquered the much of Central
Asia all the way to the Caspian Sea in
the Aral Sea and
re retook presentation Jang and Tibet
from the Chinese it would it would have
looked like it's over we it's a final
Victory but in a couple of centuries the
kusan Empire had
evaporated so time if you look it all
depends on what kind of lens you're
looking at the world with lens as in
time
period these games they will always keep
on going history occurs repeats itself
in a circular fashion there are of
History Empires rise and fall rise and
fall and when Empires are rising they
there's a certain process that happens
when Empires are in threat of Decline
and falling they lash out at the world
and that's what we are seeing with the
US it's kind of an Empire that is that
feels like it may be declining so it
wants to do whatever it can to lash out
and to consolidate its power wherever it
is and even expand its sphere of power
so as you can see you know people are
talking about the us as a declining
power well look what they just achieved
in Bangladesh look what they just
achieved in Bangladesh they now have two
proxies in the subcontinent you call
that a declining power it's not a
declining power so these games will
never end from our perspective we have
to ensure we somehow continue to rise
economically and militarily
also and it's easier said than
done
right
okay this is an interesting question
John the wise asks from X which is
Twitter what role did social networks
like Instagram Facebook Etc have in
instigating this coup can we over ever
hold the CIA accountable if they were
behind this you can never hold the CIA
accountable there is no evidence that so
and so percentage so Ando thing there is
always a tremendous amount of
confiscation and a tremendous amount of
plausible deniability in everything
these organizations do so there is no
way to hold anybody accountable and even
if you know that they've done it what
will you do about it where will you take
them to court which court your court
your country's Court ha will they
come which where how do you hold them
accountable you can't they are way too
powerful for you uh but the question is
what role did social networks have in
instigating the school while social
networks are ubiquitous today everywhere
everybody has something on their phone
on their tablet on their device
everybody is scrolling up and down all
day especially youngsters so there is a
tremend tremendous amount of influence
that social media holds over their minds
and hearts so Instagram Facebook Twitter
whatever they use Tik Tok Etc it would
have had a tremendous role to play in
instigating the coup it's so easy to
rapidly disseminate various kinds of
narratives and claims and information
misinformation whatever propaganda
political ideology speech whatever
through social networks that's how it's
done it's done on an industrial scale
all across the world so social networks
would have been very much uh at the
heart of instigating this coup and I
hear that Shina had tried to ban social
networks like X and Instagram Etc and I
also know for a fact that people were
still using the social networks in
Bangladesh so the ban looks like it
looks like the ban did not work or it
was not implemented or carried out or
executed
properly because I know that people in
Bangladesh were posting until yesterday
day before yesterday before the goo
happened while the goo
happened you can see that you can check
for yourself all these posts were coming
out so when it comes to uh instigating
coups uh interfering in elections all of
that social networks American social
networks are very much part of the of
the game plan of whoever wants to do
these
activities okay KT says if the is the
US's aim to isolate India and force of
war against China weaken China and
divide India that's killing two birds
with one stone if so is our biggest
enemy the US not
China okay good question I appreciate
the people asking good questions
incisive questions
look where where we sit where we if you
look at our geographical position in the
world in Asia in Eurasia our biggest
nebor is China our most immediate threat
is China very
clear but if you zoom out then the
biggest hegemonic power is the United
States and it has power projection all
across the globe everywhere it threatens
every
country okay it projects power over
every country it influences every
country and it essentially arm twists
every country it arm twists Europe into
accepting millions of refugees that its
people don't want it arm twists Africa
in giving up its resources for for
peanuts uh it arm twists Nations like
Japan and South Korea and Australia and
what not into hosting their military
bases on their soil and so on so forth
they have power projection all across
the world so it's about it's kind of
like looking at long-term versus
short-term threats China is immediate
it's an immediate and present danger
okay for
India but if India and China somehow
reach some kind of understanding some
kind of Modas vendi then for both
Nations the US is the biggest long-term
threat
so look India doesn't want enemity with
anybody India doesn't want enmity with
China with the US with anyone but this
is all being forced upon
us so when it's being forced upon you
you have to respond you to react and you
to take appropriate measures that's
where we
so what is the US's objective the us
from the American perspective India has
very limited
utility India for the US is a good
nation that a nation that can serve as a
good counterbalance to China so in
Eurasia the Chinese and the Russians
have some kind of understanding for for
Mutual mutually beneficial
purposes and from China's perspective
the only nation that can counter it in
Asia or challenge it in Asia or stand up
to it in Asia is India right and from
India's perspective China claims Indian
Territory China has fought a war against
India China still threatens India all
the time so from India's perspective
China is the biggest threat so from the
US perspective India's limited utility
is to counterbalance
China and that India can do by being a
reasonably strong economic and military
power but if India says that we we will
keep growing at 8% for the next 20 years
that's something that America doesn't
want they say no no no you stay where
you are if you are a three4 trillion
economy you remain a $4 trillion economy
don't try to become too big for your
boots don't try to get off the
reservation stay in your lane that's
what the the Americans want India to do
so India should stay where it is I in
the ideal scenario for the US India and
China go to war bash each other's brains
out destroy each other and then the
Americans can happily and at their own
Leisure take care of Russia that is the
ideal scenario from the US
perspective so uh that's uh the game The
Americans are playing obviously India
and China are not stupid it doesn't make
sense for India and China to go to war I
think even the Chinese are realizing
that now because if India and China go
to war and certain lines are cross then
both Nations will be destroyed both
Nations have the ability to inflict
significant damage on the other and who
stands to lose more the Chinese stand to
lose more they have a
what what what's the economy like 17
trillion or whatever it is they they
stand to lose everything they've built
over the past 30 years and India also
stands to lose a lot so what's the point
of fighting I mean India and China we
have a common border the India Tibet
border so we going to be adversaries as
long as China occupies Tibet that we
understand but for the time being it
looks like India and China may have come
to a realization or understanding that
we need to whatever conflict we have we
need to postpone for the next 5 10 years
then we'll look at it so looks like
there's this common understanding and
realization that the biggest enemy is
the shared enemy which is not in
Eurasia geographically
physically pram chra says will there be
a war between India and Pakistan as 500
SSG terrorists or Commandos or whatever
of Pakistan have entered India look I
heard reports from social media and
various news channels Etc that X number
or Y number of Pakistani uh soldiers
Commandos terrorists whatever you want
to call them have entered India
infiltrated into India and Jammu and
Kashmir well look I I don't know whether
it's true or false I don't know whether
it's right or wrong I don't know how
credible these claims are I am not on
the ground in jnk I haven't I don't have
evidence of that so it doesn't make
sense for me to comment on this I don't
know how credible these claims
are just because four or five media
networks or Outlets are making this
claim doesn't mean that this claim is
true maybe it's true maybe it's
partially true maybe it's fully true
maybe it's not true at all I don't know
so
look uh and and let's say hypothetically
500 600 of these terrorists have entered
India does it mean that we have to go to
war no you neutralize them but
eventually you have to hit at the strike
at the root of the problem which is
within in Pakistan at some point in time
we'll have to do that look Pakistan is
is a temporary Nation eventually it will
cease to
exist uh and we have to look at it that
way but right now I don't I we don't
need a war we don't want a war with
anybody right
now
okay once again same question Donald
Trump election is of any hope okay I
haven't answered this question today
I've taken it before in in the past many
times so
is there any chance that Donald Trump
will win the election look he is the
most popular politician in the US right
now okay uh he clearly is more popular
than Kamala Harris even though various
US news networks are trying to spin the
narrative and try to they're trying to
claim that Kamala Harris has more po has
more percentage points or whatever they
call it you know compared to Trump I
don't think so I I don't believe so but
even if Trump is more popular I I think
Kamala may
win because the US is not a democracy
and the election will be
rigged just like the 2020 election lots
of people allege they allege it was
rigged Donald Trump himself says that
the election was stolen so if they did
that in 2020 they'll do it again in 2024
they will not allow Trump to win unless
Trump has made some kind of deal with
the devil which we don't know if he has
so if he has made it deal with the devil
some kind of go and Kiss the Ring Of The
Godfather that sort of thing yeah then
he may win otherwise Kamala Harris or
whoever it is will win so I think it's
less likely that Trump will win it's
more likely that Kamala Harris will
win Alish nil chandani nihalani says
sorry nialani says you said the US wants
to create a Christian Nation with parts
of Bangladesh Burma mizoram and Manipur
but how is this possible as Bangladesh
is a majority Muslim country all right
sir let's go and understand the
geography there are parts of Bangladesh
that are not Muslim majority if you look
at the chatram chram hill hill tracks
it's majority Buddhist and the Buddhist
are
being you know what what is done to
Buddhists and non non-muslims in the
Muslim Nation so that is that's been
happening in the chagang hill tra for
decades um and in the vicinity of
mizoram tripura Etc there are there are
parts of Bangladesh where you have
cookies that have infiltrated and become
you know kind of a majority in some
parts so you will find that there are
parts of Bangladesh especially adjoining
Burma mizoram Etc where you may actually
have cookie majority
Christian majority so those parts of
Bangladesh will become part of this
artificial new Christian Nation mizoram
is almost exclusively Christian
now and lots of parts of Burma in which
are adjoining missor Manipur nagaland
Etc are full of these cookies who are
converted to various kinds of
Christianity mainly Baptist whatever it
is so all of that will be used to create
this new nation of kilan so please
understand I'm not saying the whole of
Bangladesh I'm saying some parts of
Bangladesh and understand where you have
those parts of Bangladesh so that's why
it's possible sir that's how it that's
how it
works
okay auran says as per news channel
fasina is going to Finland in the next
couple of days well we we will see we
will see uh that lady the Bangladeshi
lady tasa Nim is also
uh she's also got ay in some Nordic
country right so maybe maybe it could be
like
that uh geopolitical dub says China was
China success un successful in Hong Kong
when the US did the same there well you
see China is way more powerful than
India it's about three or four times
more powerful than India and it has much
more control over its territories than
India
does okay so when it comes to India's
Far East we have allowed a foreign
religion to take to take root there and
entire States entire communities entire
ethnic groups have have become
christianized and then that that's what
makes them amenable to having extra
territorial extra National loyalties in
China that sort of thing is not allowed
in China that is crushed with an iron
hand if India tries to crush things with
an iron hand we will attract us
sanctions the Chinese economy and the US
economy are joined at the hip and the
Americans can't you know impose
sanctions Beyond a certain level on
China so India and China are very
different Beast China is way more
powerful than India so they can get get
away with a lot more than India can so
that's the whole point you need to be
more powerful you need to be stronger
India's economy needs to keep growing if
India becomes a 10 trillion doll economy
the Americans won't be able to apply the
same kind of pressure as they're doing
now if India becomes a 20 trillion doll
economy the Americans will be very very
very careful with how they handle India
but right now India is a $4 trillion
dollar economy and and so on so forth
you understand how it goes right please
understand that at the end of the day
the only thing that matters is how
powerful or how weak you are and the
biggest sin the biggest sin in
geopolitics is
weakness
okay Sunil says is the Bangladesh coup a
plot to flood India with refugees like
Isis did to Europe look Isis Isis did
not do anything to Europe it
is it's somebody who flooded Europe with
Isis
refugees I mean some of these
individuals are known to have posed with
various horrible things in their hands
in this manner with something in their
hand here and this so somebody flooded
Europe with ex Isis
Fighters now let's not go into who that
somebody was and let's not go into who
created Isis
Isis did not create itself right uh but
yeah so yeah the coup in Bangladesh
could see a major surge of refugees into
India right now what we are witnessing
is a major Spate of attacks on Hindus in
Bangladesh uh what's the percentage of
Hindus that still exist in Bangladesh
maybe seven 8% of Bangladeshi are Hindus
now it used to be 30 40% I don't know
what it was few years ago few decades
ago so it's now about seven or 8% and
they are being uh persecuted right now
there is this big Spate of attacks on
Hindus and Hindu buildings and Hindu
communities and Hindu temples Hindu
temples are being burned so lots of
Hindus will probably try to cross over
into India and Escape Bangladesh
forever now seven or 8% of Bangladesh
it's still a big number so you could
have that and along with those Hindus
who trying to escape the the whatever is
happening you could also have certain
other elements who will try to cross
over into India so
yeah there definitely could be you know
this this could be part of the agenda to
try and flood India with a big Spate of
refugees of various kinds that that
could happen so that's why we have to be
very careful we have to hopefully seal
the
border every state including every
state and hopefully the BSF does that
job for a change yeah
uh okay anur says anur says in the
current situation of Bangladesh what if
the persecuted Hindu minorities come to
the Indian borders seeking safe shelter
Safe Haven into India what are the
possible steps the Indian government can
take well that's that's a that's a big
big question on the one hand these
people are being persecuted maybe they
are being killed massacred whatever one
hears all kinds of horror stories right
now right now on the phone if you see
there's all kinds of atrocities being
done against Hindus that's why I say
it's like East Pakistan has has come to
life again so now what do we do these
Hindus will obviously this what place do
they have to go there's only one place
in the world where Hindus can go that's
India and then if they successfully
cross over into India they're treated
like third class citizens not citizens
third class refugees I mean see the
Pakistani refugees in in various parts
of India how they what kind of living
conditions they have horrible horrible
anyhow
so these persecuted Hindu minorities of
Bangladesh let's say they come to the
Indian border and they want to seek safe
refuge in India what should India
do I think IND it is I think India is
Duty bound to allow them to come into
India but then how do you separate the
the genuine refugees who are genuinely
freeing fleeing
persecution from those who are trying to
take advantage of the situation and
infiltrate into India how do you
differentiate between the to that is
some that is a headache that the Indian
government will have to face and they're
going to have to find solutions to this
so either you leave the Hindus to their
fate and let them die because Hindus are
Hindus anywhere in India also are second
class citizens India is the world's most
Hindu phobic Nation so let the Hindus
die in Bangladesh that's one attitude
the Indian government can have which is
very much possible or let's say the
Indian government says we will allow the
Hindus to come in but then the problem
is lots of non-hindus will also want to
infiltrate into India and cause Mayhem
in India that could be part of the
plan so how do you solve that problem so
that's a headache the government will
have to resolve the easiest thing is let
the Hindus die and that's no big
deal M
though
okay
um okay Bobby eens is talking about the
US election not sure for Trump versus
Harris anymore Harris has chosen a weak
Governor as her Vice Presidential
nominee Tim Waltz she should have chosen
Shapiro Ben
Shapiro he would have overpowered her
and outmaneuvered her Ben Shapiro he's
like VI ramaswami on steroids isn't he
uh yeah I don't know look it doesn't
matter how good or bad the Democratic
candidates are if they're going to rig
the election whoever it is is going to
win
I'm not being cynical here okay I've
seen what happened in
2020 certain in certain places you know
the votes didn't the counting did not
happen for a few days it went on for
days and days and then there were sudden
vote you know ballot dumps and all that
clear rigging there are so many videos
on the X that were taken down very
rapidly of ballot stuffing and whatnot
so it doesn't matter whether the go the
the VP she has chosen as a weak person
or strong person doesn't matter at all
if they're going to rig it it doesn't
matter who it is so yeah that's that's
what it
is mcloven says so the us is going to
take over St Martin island what's next
are they going to bring nukes over are
we in a situation like Russia Ukraine
war possible they could perhaps mean if
if they acquire the island they can
deploy whatever they want there they
could deploy nuclear weapons you know
ballistic missiles nuclear weapons
Cruise mes with nuclear weapons they
could do that or they could do they can
use it in in a variety of ways they can
use it as as a base from which they can
launch strategic
bombers St bombers the kind of bombers
they have on on Diego Garcia or they
could it it will also be a naval base
it'll be a place where place where they
train terrorists and insurgents to fight
against India and Burma and China and
whoever else and sorry Freedom Fighters
the Americans when they train somebody
those people are never terrorists they
always Freedom Fighters it's always
for democracy right so yeah the
Americans could use it in whichever way
they want so it's obviously not good for
India to have a hostile power so close
to us to to our borders to our
Shores
okay the just says was the assassination
of BB a c as well do do you think sh K
might get assassinated in in the same
way look I hope nobody gets assassinated
U as long as shikina is in some say some
some friendly country like India or
whatever she is probably she would be
taken care of and she as long as she is
no longer politically active now then
she's no longer a threat to anyone
unless she's a symbol of
something
so I hope that such a thing doesn't
happen to her was the assassination of
bzb a coup it wasn't a coup it was the
elimination of a threat a coup is when
you take out somebody who is in power
and replace that with somebody else but
that person has to be in power okay she
was not in power she was not prime
minister at the time so that was not a
coup but whoever did this took out a
dangerous political rival that's what
happened um yeah so that's that's how I
see
that um D Shukla says this is all so
saddening look the
world is not a nice
place when we are kids we look at all
the nice things in the world all the
flowers and the birds and the
butterflies you know when you're a
toddler when you're three years old nice
bright Sunset sun sunrise clouds in the
sky butterflies in the garden you go and
Chase butterflies then you grow older
you're 10 12 years old you kind of see
the world in a different way by the time
you're 182 you're still very idealistic
and you think that there are bad things
in the world but the you know truth
prevails sat blah blah blah but over
time you will realize that there are
that the world is constantly caught in a
conflict between various Powers various
uh
agendas and it's not always truth that
wins it's not always the good guys that
win and generally when somebody is in
power for a long time they stay in power
by doing lots of naughty stuff bad stuff
okay so yeah it is saddening
what is saddening you know what is
really
saddening what is saddening is the
realization that your innocence is going
away and now you are able to see the
world in the True Light the world has
always been like this at the highest
levels the highest levels of power it's
always been like
this you know swim or or or or sink kill
or be killed eat the eat your enemy or
the enemy eats you the you know big fish
eats small fish the rule of the Jungle
that is geopolitics
it's always been like this for thousands
of
years but it's what is saddening is when
you grow up and you realize that the
world is so ugly and so evil and it's
there's no justice unless you make your
own Justice that is what's saddening so
it's something everybody has to go
through but hopefully you don't become
cynical and become all negative there is
still a lot of good in the world that
should be fought
for okay
um should India invade Bangladesh and
create a region like donet and lhans why
what do you get out of
it what do you get from it you get
sanctions us sanctions Russia is an
autarchy okay Russia is a gigantic
Nation with every single resource they
can possibly ask for which is why the US
sanctions have failed when it comes to
India if the US imposes sanctions on
India it will devastate India and
Destroy India's
economy so why invade Bangladesh what do
you get out of
it what's the point look if you do
something it has to have a clear
objective which and an acquiring that
objective should outweigh all the risks
you take you have to look at it from a
game from a game theory perspective not
from the perspective of emotions that we
will go and take this and take that no
it's not the world doesn't work like
that you have to be very rational you
have to keep your emotions aside you
have to think coldly cooly calmly
numerically strategically and tactically
there's no point doing this what dones
luhans we don't have any such
regions that are pro-india see so
doesn't make sense sir
unfortunately VI man says can we create
our own education system and ecosystem
to replace the rotten anti-hat system
well one would have hope that Mr Modi
and his government would have started
something of that sort in the past 10
years but nothing has happened it
certainly is possible it has been done
in the past I mean if you go back to the
1920s the great Shri Mustafa kimal
Ataturk completely revamped the
education system of turkey after after
he liberated the country from the
West completely revamped the entire
education system it was just as
entrenched as the current Indian
education system is he changed
everything he changed the entire Society
of turkey just one
man he changed the script in which the
Turkish language is written he
essentially created a new script for
Turkish the Latin script with some
adaptations and uh yeah he he totally
transformed it it has been done the
Israelis did that they created a whole
education system out of scratch with
Hebrew as the as the language of
instruction in Turkey it was a Turkish
language the Chinese did that they
completely revamped their education
system beginning the N late 80s early
90s onwards the Chinese invested
trillions of dollars into their new
education system it is possible if the
if if the leadership has a has has the
vision and the will and if they
understand that we need better education
system because without that the future
of the country is there's no future so
it is possible it is certainly possible
but we have to raise our standards and
and and and say no to all the
mediocrity but right now unfortunately
our entire system is run on the basis of
mediocrity so it's it's uh very
disappointing that nothing has been done
in the past 10 years not even a start
there is something called the new
education policy which is a joke the new
education policy does not address any of
the fundamental structural issues that
plague the Indian education system it
does nothing of that sort it is it is an
exercise in cosmetics it's like a
putting lipstick on the lips of a
pig it's like putting a Band-Aid on a
gunshot wound so it is certainly
possible to do that we we have done we
had a great education system in the past
we certainly can have it
again but uh we will need better
leadership for
that
okay uh CL says your views on the UK
riats well inevitable what do you expect
when you flood a nation with people who
hate the nation and at some point in
time you're going to see some kind of uh
reaction from the
natives and obviously the UK government
is
anti-native they're accusing the natives
of being violent and they are completely
overlooking what the Invaders The
Invader settlers whatever you want to
call them are doing so um I think the UK
is doomed I think the West is doomed
Europe Western Europe is doomed they're
going to be replaced genetically
socially culturally religiously they're
going to be replaced it's the
replacement is happening it is being
engineered and in in the case of the UK
well I would say it's
karma I kind of feel sorry for the
natives to some at some level I kind of
feel sorry for them but on another level
I I immediately remember what they did
to my people to our people so then I say
what's the right term soovi it soovi
it soovi
it
um dongar Singh Chan takes us to a
different place to Iran how do you think
Iran will will retaliate are you
foreseeing a big war in the Middle East
considering Russia's involvement
um I I don't see Iran being able to
retaliate to the Israeli actions in a
big way Iran doesn't have the Air Force
that's capable of of flying a thousand
kilometers striking Israel successfully
and then returning safely another
thousand kilometers it has good drones
and good ballistic missiles but the
Israelis have excellent defense systems
the Iron Dome which can take out the
majority of the drones and the missiles
so the last time they did a big attack
it was kind of unsuccessful it did not
take out any big targets any high value
targets most of the drones and missiles
were shot down by the Israelis and by
the by the Saudis and
jordanians so and the Saudis are saying
that we will not allow Iran to uh to
launch any aircraft drones whatever over
Saudi over Saudi airspace so how does
Iran retaliate against Israel how do
they do it they're going to have to do
it through proxis Hezbollah or whatever
Yemen huis hisbah Hamas or something
like that the Russians won't get
involved
directly so how does Iran do it is the
question so they will try because they
have been humiliated if if what they are
claiming is true it is a big humiliation
for them and they're going to have to
find a Face
Saver how do they do it is a big
question uh so right now I don't see a
major war in the Middle East how how do
two countries go to war when they are a
thousand kilometers apart very hard to
do that you know so I don't see a big
what happening just yet just
yet
uh om biker says can India seal the
border with Bangladesh without damaging
ties too much as Bangladesh might now
host anti-india forces Bangladesh now
definitely hosts anti-india
forces the ties are already
damaged it's an anti-india government
that's in power now it's a it's a
western backed government Muhammad yunus
is playing a very dirty game he is there
okay let me not make any comparisons
with Indian politicians but he's there
one of our politicians let's just say it
that way we have had multiple
politicians in the past that have played
the kind of
role which that that Muhammad un is
playing right now okay I'll not name
anybody so uh we already have a strongly
anti-india government in Bangladesh now
it's it's in the process of formation
but Bangladesh is essentially a new East
Pakistan so India should seal the border
the BSF needs to be extremely Vigilant
the Indian army should be extremely
Vigilant not a
single
uh let's say hostile element should be
allowed to cross the border so India is
going to be have to be very very
Vigilant light right now and don't worry
about damaging ties to hell with the
ties our national security is more
important than the perceived
state of our ties with the two
Nations okay
okay VII Manar says can't we civilians
replace the education system of bat
instead of relying on the government are
we so spineless look the question is how
do we let's say you or let's say me I
want to create a new education system
how do I do it well I'll have to at
least set up a school or a college or a
university I tell you first set up a
school then a college then a university
right so do you understand how much
money it takes to do that you have to
hire staff you have to create an
entirely new syllabus on your own or
with the help of your staff you have to
hire people who are genuinely qualified
who are who are aligned with you your
vision of how the education system
should be should be able to give impart
the right skills to the students at
whichever level you to pay their
salaries you have to have the
establishment the building the land the
equipment all that you're talking about
hundreds of crores of rupees just for
one one something that one person is
essentially doing
right where do you get the money from
most people don't have that sort of
money right and even if you create your
system like that the government
will most likely not
recognize what you're doing if you're
offering so and so degree they'll say
your degree is not valid because it is
not in line with whatever system they
have then how do you do it
you can homeschool your kid your kid or
kids and hopefully give them the ski
skills that you want but that has has
its own challenges that's why see
ideally the government of India whose
job it is to serve the nation it is they
who are supposed to do this for
individuals it is extremely difficult to
do this unless they have access to
tremendous amounts of money and that is
the problem you could bring the right
kind of people together the people who
have the right ideas and the right
vision
and the ability to execute on those
ideas and the vision but you would also
have to connect them with a big source
of money some philanthropist or somebody
who can give let's say 100 crores every
two years or three years or something
like that so it's it's not an easy task
but then you would also need that your
degrees and all that to be recognized by
the government without which this the
students whom you teaching they may do
very poorly in their careers they may
not get jobs so there are all these
problems right
that's the
problem ches Khan par says both Pakistan
and Bangladesh are totally dependent on
India for water and food why do
anti-india forces there think they can
continue how are they dependent on India
Pakistan and India don't trade at all
Pakistan we are not exporting anything
anymore to Pakistan they're not
dependent on India for food uh yeah most
of the water that comes into Pakistan
comes through India the indust rivers
treaty and all that but we are not in a
position to stop to cut off the flow of
water because we have not built a single
Dam on those Rivers where they passed
through our territory so what has
prevented our governments over the past
10 20 30 00 300 years to build from
building those dams we haven't done that
so that tells you that India is not in a
position to cut off the supply of water
to Pakistan and the same goes for
Bangladesh so there's nothing India can
do when it comes to food I think the
Pakistan is
Bangladesh is have lots of various
options when it comes to food so it is
not really the case like we imagine it
is we have to be practical and
realistic
okay Malik said happy birthday sir happy
birthday really wish you a very happy
birthday any tips and guidance look
you've got to achieve your potential in
life uh you got to work very hard and
also have a lot of fun in the process
okay
the main objective in life is to give
back more to society than you take from
it and hopefully have a lot of fun along
the way and be happy along the way so
that's what I would say and always like
I say have high standards high standards
okay so I wish you all the best you I
wish you a very happy 18th birthday and
do well for yourself and do well for for
our people for the whole of
society happy birthday
again mamad says what about Muhammad
yunice is he going to become the new
prime minister in Bangladesh and why and
if yes will he be a puppet of the US
look I'll tell you what yeah most likely
Muhammad unus is going to be the new
prime minister they will call it an
interim prime minister care carer prime
minister whatever okay but it looks like
he's going to be the next prime minister
in Bangladesh and he is extremely
beholden to the West he's extremely
friendly to the West uh he has had he
has been given so many honors by the
West I believe he has the no prize yes
uh Muhammad yunus does he have a Nobel
Prize let's Google it quickly I think he
has let me go to Google our friend
Google uh
mamad
yunus um let's see what prize does he
have ah Nobel priest prize there you go
he has been given the Nobel priest prize
so when you have somebody from the
subcontinent India Pakistan Sri Lanka
Bangladesh or any third world nation who
either has a Nobel Prize not in science
but in some other field or who has
something like the mag Prize or whatever
then you can be pretty sure that they
are deeply beholden to the West okay
this
gentleman is right now living outside of
Bangladesh but he will now return to
Bangladesh and he will return as a great
Conquering Hero and he will become the
Prime Minister most likely and he will
very much be the be a puppet of the US
he's going to
to the line this entire thing this
entire coup has been stage managed by
the US and they will ensure that their
guy that their their man will be in
power and he will do exactly what they
tell him to do so that's how it's going
to go he is going to be most likely the
next prime minister and he going to be a
us
asset
okay let's take a couple more questions
um
geopolitical dub says now the IMF is
ready to help Bangladesh obviously they
will help look the IMF is is an
organization that's controlled by the
west by the US so now that there's a pro
US Government there obviously they will
Bangladesh no big surprises
there vov says is there a possibility of
a similar situation happening in China
what will the situation look like post
the fall of the PRC look the Chinese
ches government is a very different
beast and China is a very very tightly
controlled extremely opaque Nation you
don't know what's happening
inside and it is believed that the
Chinese Communist party was also
compromised and infiltrated by the
Americans in the
2000s and after shinpin came to power in
the 2010s all
those us assets were identified and
taken care of lots of high rcking
Chinese commun high ranking middle
ranking low ranking CCP
officials were purged they disappeared
and bad things happened to them so the
possibility of a coup happening in China
a US managed coup is very low it's very
low I'm sure the US still would have
some clandestine assets within the
Chinese Communist Party The Americans
are are the best in the world at these
things it infiltrating Nations and
compromising organizations Etc they're
great there's nobody better than than
the Americans at this so I'm sure that
the Americans have assets within China
but will they be able to pull off what
they in Bangladesh I think it would be
very difficult for them to do that but
if the PRC Falls then there could be a a
period of chaos and Anarchy in China and
China Lots the moment the PRC Falls
whenever it happens in the future lots
of territories will secede from China
and declare independence just like what
happened in the USSR after the fall of
the USSR that would
happened
okay
um say Sam says what's the okay let's
end this session with this question okay
what is the US end goal why have they
staged the cool in Bangladesh and what
do they want to achieve at the end
what's the end goal the coup is aimed at
India they have no real interest in
Bangladesh okay it's it's all about
geography let's take a look at the
geography it's all about encircling
India here we have India so on the west
of India we have an American proxy
Pakistan northwest of Pakistan you have
Afghanistan which is ruled by the
Taliban which is essentially again an
American proxy
okay
uh south of India you have Sri Lanka
which has American influence
uh Thailand is is is very much under the
control of the US the Americans can
unleash uh student protests there on
demand uh Burma is in a in a state of
Civil War which is again being Unleashed
by the
Americans Bangladesh is a US proxy now
okay Nepal is a Chinese proxy so India
is completely encircled India is cut off
from the rest of the world Pakistan Cuts
cuts off India's access to Eurasia from
the West China is occupies occupied
Tibet cuts of India's access to Northern
Asia from the
north um
Burma is until recently has been an open
Nation but now there is a civil war and
once this artificial new nation cooki
land will be formed it will cut off
India's Nation to Eastern Asia so India
will be completely cut off by land from
all parts of the world the only access
we will have to the rest of the world is
by is by sea or by air the seas are
controlled by the Americans they have
the world's largest network of military
bases all across the world and the and
the uh air is also controlled by the
Americans so that is not good for India
we are cut off from the rest of the
world and whatever access we have it
goes through American jurisdiction and
American uh
strongholds so that gives the US
complete control over India's Destiny
and they can use these assets like
Pakistan and East Pakistan Bangladesh to
destabilize India in a variety of ways
the new kand will also be used to
destabilize India's Far East create all
kinds of Mayhem in Manipur and other
parts of the Far East so overall India
gets destabilized badly so India doesn't
reach its economic potential instead of
growing at 8% every year India grows at
4% every year so by 2035 instead of
becoming a 10 125 trillion economy India
is just a 5 trilon dollar economy that
is the end goal of the US they are
worried about India's rise they don't
want India to become a long-term
adversary and India has the potential to
become a long-term adversary from their
perspective so they are doing this is
called long-term planning we will nip
things in the blood in the blood right
now and we will put conditions in place
right now which will ensure that India
never Rises India remains mediocre and
we're going to create artificial
divisions and in within India just like
the British used to do divide and
conquer that is the end goal the
objective the real Target is not
Bangladesh the real Target is
India that's the deal okay I'm going to
end this live stream at this point thank
you so much for all your questions I'm
going to do another live stream on
Friday by that time we will have more
information some more time we have
elapsed so we will have a probably
slightly better understanding of where
things stand so yeah
so that's it for me for today and thank
you so much for all your
questions I'll talk to you again on
Friday and we will revisit this entire
matter at the time until then take care
thank you so much keep raising your
standards and I'll see you very soon bye